Buzzinga.
(Sheldon:)Leonard and Penny.
(Sheldon:)-Leonard and Penny.
-Aah!
LEONARD:
What? What, what, what?
[LEONARD & PENNY SIGH]
(Sheldon:)Leonard and Penny.
(Leonard(Waking up as Penny screams):)-What?
-I have good news.
(Leonard:)And you had to barge in
and wake us up...
(Leonard:)-...in the middle of the night?
-Your cell phone was off.
(Leonard:)Because we didn't
wanna be disturbed.
(Sheldon:)That didn't work out, did it?
(Penny:)Sheldon, what do you want?
(Sheldon:)I came to tell you I've got the answer.
(Leonard:)Really?
(Leonard:)You figured out
the graphene problem?
(Sheldon:)No, I'm still hopelessly stuck on that.
But I figured out how to figure it out.
(Penny:)I know I said I could handle
your roommate, but I was wrong.
We have to break up.